Sir, what is your opinion on yesterday's quarterly numbers
?  Let's start with the best number
and that is ICICI Piden, it is showing good strong results.
Gross
premium income has improved across all parameters.  VNB
margins
are fine.  Profits also appeared to be better than expected.
So the numbers are good on every scale.
Correct?  The only thing is that there are
signs of a slight slowdown in overall growth.  There is such strong growth.
Slowdown in growth is not negative.   There
is a difference between the two.  There
is a difference between low growth and negative growth.  So
lightly he is.  Ah stock chaki thoda kal bhi toh hai.
Due to this, the potential was up by 3.5% yesterday
and has decreased by only 10% in 3 months.
So the valuations are definitely a bit expensive.
That's why let's see.  I believe that one should
buy around the support level.   There
is support at 535 540.  On the upside it may
try to go up to 5850.  So
among the three results, this one has the highest scope for growth.
Second is ICICI LBRD numbers, I did
not like its numbers which were mixed.
Meaning, it is not as powerful as
I wanted it to be.  You can tell from the mix.
Ah, the number is not like the 6.5% rise the stock has seen yesterday.
And the biggest thing is that
this share has not fallen much.  It has
decreased only by 3.5% in 3 months.  It has decreased only by 4%.
So this is an increased share.  Firstly,
this is not a number which is higher than the other.
Its support levels are 1785 and 1800.
I am giving these futures levels.  On the upside,
it will be seen strengthening only above 1860 and 1865.
So if it opens with a big gap then profit
booking will be seen.  And if it does
not open with a big gap and comes down then it will get some support.  The
third is IREDA.  We Too Good to
Believe kind of number.  Well, the
numbers are coming out very strong every quarter.  57% Net
Interest Income Profit Increase by 50%
NPA is also good at Gross Net level.  There is no
problem with the numbers.
Nums is awesome.  There
is the same problem tomorrow.  Yesterday 9% of it ran away.  The
market has deteriorated the most in the last one month.  It does
n't matter to him.  One year one BSE de just
ignore the market.  Completely deadly.  Royally
yes.  20% raise in a month?  20% 20%
In such a market, good numbers are available at a good price.   It
is an expensive stock, if it comes at some support
around 158 then buy it, on the higher side there are
levels of 173 178, ok sir you will share the stock of the day at 9:00 am.
Exactly at 9:00 and at
9:00 we have news on some gas stocks as well.
We will have a complete analysis on that for you there at 9:00.  Done.   Let
's go but move on